Contact

afrinathar29@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/afrinathar-82a7b9bb (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Node.js React and Redux D3.js

Afrin Athar

R&D Engineer at Dassault Systèmes
Pune

Summary

Experienced Product Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry . Skilled in React , Redux , Node.js, AngularJS, D3.js and JavaScript. Strong professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science from Birla Institute of Technology, Ranchi.

Experience

Dassault Systèmes

1 year

R&D Engineer April 2020 - Present (5 months)

Pune, Maharashtra

R&D Associate Engineer September 2019 - March 2020 (7 months)

Pune, Maharashtra

Riverus - the legal insight company Associate Product Developer September 2018 - August 2019 (1 year) Pune Area, India

Prakshep Front End Intern January 2018 - June 2018 (6 months) Bangalore

Wipro Summer Intern May 2017 - June 2017 (2 months) Jaipur Area, India

Indian Institute of Management, Indore

Winter Intern

December 2016 - December 2016 (1 month)

Developed the research engine for data analysis using MS Excel and Visual Basic Application (VBA)

Education

Birla Institute of Technology, Ranchi Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2014 - 2018)

Sophia Senior Secondary School